const questionsData = [{"index": 1, "question": "Soru 1 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 2, "question": "Soru 2 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 3, "question": "Soru 3 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 4, "question": "Soru 4 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 5, "question": "Soru 5 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 6, "question": "Soru 6 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 7, "question": "Soru 7 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 8, "question": "Soru 8 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 9, "question": "Soru 9 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 10, "question": "Soru 10 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 11, "question": "Soru 11 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 12, "question": "Soru 12 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 13, "question": "Soru 13 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 14, "question": "Soru 14 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 15, "question": "Soru 15 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 16, "question": "Soru 16 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 17, "question": "Soru 17 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 18, "question": "Soru 18 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 19, "question": "Soru 19 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 20, "question": "Soru 20 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 21, "question": "Soru 21 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 22, "question": "Soru 22 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 23, "question": "Soru 23 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 24, "question": "Soru 24 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 25, "question": "Soru 25 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 26, "question": "Soru 26 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 27, "question": "Soru 27 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 28, "question": "Soru 28 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 29, "question": "Soru 29 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 30, "question": "Soru 30 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 31, "question": "Soru 31 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 32, "question": "Soru 32 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 33, "question": "Soru 33 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 34, "question": "Soru 34 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 35, "question": "Soru 35 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 36, "question": "Soru 36 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 37, "question": "Soru 37 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 38, "question": "Soru 38 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 39, "question": "Soru 39 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 40, "question": "Soru 40 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 41, "question": "Soru 41 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 42, "question": "Soru 42 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 43, "question": "Soru 43 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 44, "question": "Soru 44 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 45, "question": "Soru 45 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 46, "question": "Soru 46 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 47, "question": "Soru 47 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 48, "question": "Soru 48 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 49, "question": "Soru 49 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 50, "question": "Soru 50 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 51, "question": "Soru 51 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 52, "question": "Soru 52 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 53, "question": "Soru 53 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 54, "question": "Soru 54 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 55, "question": "Soru 55 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 56, "question": "Soru 56 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 57, "question": "Soru 57 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 58, "question": "Soru 58 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 59, "question": "Soru 59 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 60, "question": "Soru 60 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 61, "question": "Soru 61 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 62, "question": "Soru 62 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 63, "question": "Soru 63 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 64, "question": "Soru 64 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 65, "question": "Soru 65 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 66, "question": "Soru 66 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 67, "question": "Soru 67 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 68, "question": "Soru 68 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 69, "question": "Soru 69 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 70, "question": "Soru 70 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 71, "question": "Soru 71 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 72, "question": "Soru 72 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 73, "question": "Soru 73 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 74, "question": "Soru 74 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 75, "question": "Soru 75 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 76, "question": "Soru 76 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 77, "question": "Soru 77 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 78, "question": "Soru 78 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 79, "question": "Soru 79 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 80, "question": "Soru 80 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 81, "question": "Soru 81 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 82, "question": "Soru 82 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 83, "question": "Soru 83 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 84, "question": "Soru 84 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 85, "question": "Soru 85 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 86, "question": "Soru 86 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 87, "question": "Soru 87 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 88, "question": "Soru 88 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 89, "question": "Soru 89 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 90, "question": "Soru 90 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 91, "question": "Soru 91 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 92, "question": "Soru 92 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 93, "question": "Soru 93 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 94, "question": "Soru 94 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 95, "question": "Soru 95 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 96, "question": "Soru 96 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 97, "question": "Soru 97 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 98, "question": "Soru 98 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 99, "question": "Soru 99 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 100, "question": "Soru 100 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 101, "question": "Soru 101 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 102, "question": "Soru 102 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 103, "question": "Soru 103 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 104, "question": "Soru 104 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 105, "question": "Soru 105 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 106, "question": "Soru 106 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 107, "question": "Soru 107 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 108, "question": "Soru 108 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 109, "question": "Soru 109 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 110, "question": "Soru 110 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 111, "question": "Soru 111 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 112, "question": "Soru 112 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 113, "question": "Soru 113 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 114, "question": "Soru 114 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 115, "question": "Soru 115 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 116, "question": "Soru 116 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 117, "question": "Soru 117 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}], "isShown": False}, {"index": 118, "question": "Soru 118 burada olacak.", "options": [{"text": "Şık 2", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 3", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 4", "isCorrect": False}, {"text": "Şık 1", "isCorrect": True}], "isShown": False}];

export default questionsData;